upscportal.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy | IAS UPSC EXAM PORTAL - India's Largest Community for UPSC, Civil Services Exam Aspirants.

##  Privacy Policy

IASEXAMPORTAL.com, is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be stored and treated. This policy may change from time to time.

**Information Collection and Use**

Registration : A user can register in order to get regular newsletter and other services where login is required. During registration, a user is required to provide certain information, such as name, address, e-mail address and password. Newsletter Services is powered by Google and it requires only email address, you can unsubscribe anytime you want.

**Use of Information**

The information that you supply to IASEXAMPORTAL enables us to provide services which are relevant to you. In addition, IASEXAMPORTAL uses your information in order to customize our site to your interests and enhance your overall experience at our site. IASEXAMPORTAL tries to recognize you using various methods, including having you log in with your e-mail address and your password. Once IASEXAMPORTAL recognizes you, pages, advertisements and other content may be customized for you so that you can see what interests you the most. In addition, as described above, IASEXAMPORTAL utilizes passive information to learn more about how you interact with our site. This passive information may be combined with your other information for purposes such as testing and improving your experience at our site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes and for disclosure to third parties such as advertisers and content partners. This aggregate passive information does not contain any personal information that can identify any individual user.

Contacting You by E-Mail : IASEXAMPORTAL may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding updates at the website. In addition, we may send you free informational newsletters or notices relating to topics that may be of special interest to you. You can leave Newsletter service anytime you want. E-mail messages from third parties are not governed by the opt-out provisions of this Privacy Policy, but all such third parties are strongly encouraged to include opt-out procedures in their messages to you.

**Sharing of Information**

IASEXAMPORTAL does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with IASEXAMPORTAL under partnership agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help IASEXAMPORTAL communicate with you about offers from IASEXAMPORTAL and our marketing partners.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.
  * Your IASEXAMPORTAL account Information is password-protected.

**Other Provisions**

_Acceptance of Terms / Changes to Privacy Policy_ \-- Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. IASEXAMPORTAL reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our site, please [Contact Us](http://www.iasexamportal.com/civilservices/contact).
